<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Olanrewaju Abidogun</title>
    <description>Olanrewaju Abidogun's blog where he showcase his portfolio and blog about his profession and life generally.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 20:45:29 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 20:45:29 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.3.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>I Started Blogging Again</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hy, this is my new blog and my first post after a very long time, I started blogging in 2015 during my Student Industrial Workshop Experience Scheme (SIWES) which was part of my required courses while I was in 300 level. I created a &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;jekyll&lt;/a&gt; blog as one of my project and ever since then, I only published twice on the platform (The day I created the blog and 31st December, 2016) ….too bad hun? It’s not really my fault, I’m not the writing type, I find it difficult and stressful most times to pen down my thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I have decided to pick it up from where I stopped and make it better. I started by creating a portfolio to showcase my myself and projects I’ve worked on, I also designed a new blog using &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.jack003.com/&quot;&gt;Jack’s’&lt;/a&gt; theme on &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com&quot;&gt;github&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Henceforth, I will be writing about about stuffs I’ve learnt while developing applications, I might focus mainly on web applications for now, since I’m learning datascience and machine learning, I will also be writing about the little things I know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now how do I intend to keep up with this and not drop it off like I did the first time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S: Its not like there are no stuffs to write, but I’m just too lazy to write and I really want to work on this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One way you can help me in achieving this is to initiate discussion on my post, this will help me keep up to it and learn more so I can write better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned…Till I write again! #Gracias.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/life/2017/03/05/I-started-blogging-again.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/life/2017/03/05/I-started-blogging-again.html</guid>
        
        <category>blogging</category>
        
        <category>new</category>
        
        <category>progress</category>
        
        <category>success</category>
        
        
        <category>LIFE</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
